Guide to the Perrine family papers, 1793-1908.
Perrine family papers, 1793-1908
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Perrine family papers, 1793-1908.
3946
.5 cubic ft.
Letters, legal documents, broadsides
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Material concerning the Perrine and Frost families, including diplomas of George Gustavus Perrine and Nesbit F. Frost; marriage certificate of W. D. Perrine and Lucinda S. Kendig, June 30, 1985; genealogical charts of the Perrine family; cypher book, receipt, military appointment and discharge and last will of Peter Perrine; and correspondence of the Perrine family.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Material concerning the Perrine and Frost families, including diplomas of George Gustavus Perrine and Nesbit F. Frost; marriage certificate of W. D. Perrine and Lucinda S. Kendig, June 30, 1985; genealogical charts of the Perrine family; cypher book, receipt, military appointment and discharge and last will of Peter Perrine; and correspondence of the Perrine family.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Perrine family.; Frost family.; Frost, Nesbit F.; Kendig, Lucinda S.; Perrine, George Gustavus.; Perrine, Peter.; Perrine, W. D.
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.; Diplomas.; Genealogies.; Marriage certificates.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1816-1825 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1830-1832 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1843-1846, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mss. Vol.: "Peter Perrine His Book", 1793-1794 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Legal Documents, 1770, 1826, 1845 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Mss. Vol. by George G. Perrine: "Copy of Record & Dates of the Perrine Family collected by Mrs. J. F. Messick (Jane LaRue Perrine) of Somerville, N.J., Dec. 1879", 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Perrine Family Genealogy (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "The Perine House" - Staten Island Historical Society article, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Receipts, Poetry, 1804, 1814, 1843, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Material related to the Dodd Family, and to Reverend Obadiah Holmes (Box 1, Folder 10)
- D.S.: George Gustavus Perrine from General Protestant Episcopal Theological Seminary, June 29, 1865 (Folder 1)
- D.S.: Perrine, Deacon, by Arthur Cleveland Coxe, July 2, 1865 (Folder 1)
- D.S.: Perrine, by Arthur Cleveland Coxe. May 27, 1866 (Folder 1)
- Broadside: W. D. Perrine reward for robber of jewelry shop (Folder 1)
- New York State Militia Commission: Peter Perrine, signed by Morgan Lewis, 1806 (Folder 1)
- New York State Mlitia Commission: Peter Perrine, Signed by Daniel D. Tompkins, 1810 (Folder 1)
- Bookkeeping diploma, Nesbit F. Frost, Pottsville, Pa., 1908 (Folder 1)